hi I'm putting together a special team
we're gonna be doing one thing one thing
on killing Nazis sound good yes I'm
gonna assume you know who we are
everybody in the German armies heard of
you you probably heard we ain't in the
prisoner taking business we're into
killing Nazi business and cousin
business is a-booming whoever wanna eat
a sauerkraut sandwich again take your
winters need so they can finger and boy
out on this map but I wanna know I
respectfully refuse hey darling got
German here what's that country the bla
him
an American Secret Service head that
lives deep behind enemy lines
the Germans call them the bastards
these Yanks have been then the devil
were article huge say that Germans
hotter in a gala premiere in attendance
will be most the German High Command
will run to do with our double agent
she'll take it from there
you're getting us in that premiere it's
suicide what else we got to go home so
what's the plan
we punch those goons out to take their
machine guns and tarsal engineers
blasting that's a plan that's about it
or not there's something you don't know
it nice attendings getting a whack on
paid off makes this a horse different
color we have all our rotten eggs in one
basket the objective of your operation
blow up the basket
we'll give you little some can take off
yeah getting cryptic good you know in
the hands of the SS my hands to be exact
and I know yes yes yes yes